quiz_data1 = [
    {
        "question": "What is food security?",
        "options": [
            "Having enough food for one day",
            "Having physical and economic access to sufficient, safe, nutritious food",
            "Having a secure place to store food",
            "Having enough money to buy food"
        ],
        "correct": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of these is a major cause of food insecurity?",
        "options": [
            "Poverty",
            "Abundance of food",
            "Too many grocery stores",
            "High literacy rates"
        ],
        "correct": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Which factor does NOT contribute to food insecurity?",
        "options": [ 
            "Conflict and war",
            "Climate change",
            "Stable government policies",
            "Economic instability"
        ],
        "correct": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Which region is most affected by food insecurity?",
        "options": [ 
            "Sub-Saharan Africa",
            "Western Europe",
            "North America",
            "East Asia"
        ],
        "correct": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "What percentage of the world's population suffers from hunger?",
        "options": [ 
            "8%",
            "10%",
            "20%",
            "30%"
        ],
        "correct": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Which organization focuses on eradicating hunger globally?",
        "options": [ 
            "World Food Programme (WFP)",
            "World Health Organization (WHO)",
            "International Monetary Fund (IMF)",
            "United Nations Educational, Scientific and Cultural Organization (UNESCO)"
        ],
        "correct": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "What is one solution to food insecurity?",
        "options": [
            "Help others with their math homework",
            "Give people in poorer countries a plane ticket to the US",
            "Don't give people in need any money",
            "Proper funding for countries in need towards their quality of agriculture and technology."
        ],
        "correct": 3
    },

    {
        "question": "Developed countries",
        "options": [
            "have low levels of food security and less waste",
            "have less food than they need and low levels of waste",
            "have more food than they need and high levels of waste",
            "have high levels of food security and low levels of waste"
        ],
        "correct": 2
    },

    {
        "question": "There is enough food produced in the world to feed everyone.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "correct": 0
    },

    {
        "question": "If your a country has high food security, can people still be undernourished",
        "options": [
            "Yes",
            "No"
        ],
        "correct": 0
    }
]